Trong Duc

IT Supervisor | Male | 21/07/1989



Experience 5 years

Latest company Brother Industries Vietnam, Ltd as IT

Supervisor

Highest education Bachelors

Languages English - Advanced

Email trongduc.hd89@gmail.com

Phone 0972842006

Address Number 3, Dong Nien Street, Hai

Duong City

SUMMARY

Hello,

My name is Duc. I'm 28 years old and I really love IT jobs.

I received Bachelors of Information Technology from Thang Long University. Additionally, I hold CCNA certificate and reach 650 TOEIC points. I can work in English fluently.

I have been a part of the IT industry for more than 5 years. During my career, I have worked in Hai Duong city, mostly working with Server and Networking devices. In other hand, I have worked with many other equipment: firewall appliances, fingerprint reader system, card reader system, camera, backup device,...

I enjoy exploring IT world with new technology and skills, mostly with system and platform.



I'm very teamworked person that work well with everyone. My style is "leard hard, work hard, play hard". I like challenging myself to do the same job with another way. When I'm not in front of computer, I'm usually traveling to explore hidden treasures in nature.

I really hope that you can give me opportunity to join your company, that would be great.

Please take a look at my attached profile any my custom profile (Resume.pdf) in online profile for more detail.

Thank you and have a nice day!

SKILL

- Computer
- Presentation
- Server
- Programing
- UPS System
- Telephone System
- Network/infrastructure
- Firewall Checkpoint
- Server / Network Administrator for Datacenter Support
- Network CCNA
- Netwoking
- SQL Server (2012, 2008)
- System Admin, IT Support
- Excellent English Proficiency
- Computer Science or Management of Infromation Sytem
- 3-5 Years in In-depth and Solidwork Experience About IT Management & Support Fileds



- Finger Print Management
- Card Readers Management

WORK EXPERIENCE

10/2016 - Present

IT Supervisor

Brother Industries Vietnam, Ltd

Additional jobs:

- Training IT jobs for other staffs
- Working with storage and NAS
- Study Virtualization
- Manage improve activity of IT Dept.

How my manager think about me: "His communication and working style is great. A very respondsible supervisor."

09/2014 - 09/2016

IT Assistant Supervisor

Brother Industries Vietnam, Ltd

I spend the majority of my day working with switch, server and firewall.

- Planing and deploying server system (File server, SQL server, Web server, Application server).
- Troubleshooting server and switch problem
- Deeply understand firewall system
- Improving and monitoring SQL server performance



- Improving security system for server
- Planing and deploying backup solution for servers
- Planing and deploying UPS solution for server
- Planing and deploying security policy for server and server room.
- Managing annual budget for network system.

How my manager think about me: "He has great problem& solving skill with deep knowledge about IT. He know how to comuticate with other people".

07/2012 - 09/2014

IT staff

Brother Industries Vietnam, Ltd

I spend the majority of my day working with telephone system, switch, fingerprint system and card reader system.

During this time, I developed fingerprint management system.

How my manager think about me: "He is very smart and hardworking. His report is easy to understand. I like the way he use English - simple but understandable."

11/2011 - 04/2012

Programmer

Pingcom, Ltd

I worked with C# and Java programing language.

Worked on project that bring presentation on mobile device.

EDUCATION



01/2016 - 01/2017

CCNA

Bachelors - Cisco

Cisco Certificate

11/2015 - 11/2015

TOEIC

Others - TOEIC

Get 650 points in TOEIC exam test.

08/2007 - 08/2011

Information Technology

Bachelors - Thang Long University

Type: Very good

